(忆往昔)
我不想跟别的猎人合作  鲍比
I don't want another hunter, Bobby.
你干嘛不来
Why can't you do it?
好吧
Fine.
那家伙叫啥
What's his name?
盖思  有啥情况
Yeah, Garth, what do you got?
最好把这事儿告诉联邦调查局
Better drop a dime to the FBI.
你是迪恩吗
Hey. You Dean?
我还以为你会高点儿
Hmm. I thought you'd be taller.
这个瘦皮猴是干嘛的
W-what's with the scrawny guy?
临时搭档
Temp.
威利斯  联邦调查局
Willis. FBI.
不  盖思  不是打给我
No, Garth, not me,
是打给真正的联邦调查局
the FBI. The real FBI.
马默杜克  真够疯狂的
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy!
你怎么活到现在的
How are you still alive?
我都错过什么了
What'd I miss?
(如今)
很久以前  就在这片树林里
Long ago, in these very woods,
住着一个老妇人  名字叫做
Lived an old woman by the name...
詹妮·格林奇
of Jenny Greentree.
全家死于火灾后  她无家可归
Forced out after her family was killed in a fire,
她失去了一切
she lost everything.
甚至有人说她已经失去人性了
Some say, even her humanity.
太凄惨了
That is so sad.
是真人真事  雷  看呀
It's a true story, Ray. Look.
她在死前把姓名首字母
She carved her initials into that tree...
刻在了那棵树上
right before she died.
那才不是她的姓名首字母
Those are not her initials.
那她怎么死的
So, how'd she die?
有一晚  一场暴风雪袭来
One night... a blizzard hit.
她又饥又冻
She's cold. She's hungry.
没有地方去  没有人帮她
Nowhere to go. No one to turn to.
詹妮·格林奇
Jenny Greentree froze to death...
就在那棵树下
right beneath...
活活冻死了
that tree.
那之后  她的恶灵就一直在这片树林里游荡
And her evil spirit has haunted these woods ever since.
别这样
Don't do that!
你们真该看看你们的表情
You guys should have seen your faces.
搞什么  特雷弗  一点都不好笑
What the hell, Trevor? That's not funny, man.
我觉得超搞笑
To you!
你开车来的吗
Yo did you drive here, man?
拜托
Ahh, please.
这样  不如你拿
Look, why-- why don't you take--
拿我的电话吧
take my phone, okay?
向老爸打小报告
Call Dad and bust me, why don't ya?
不  我的意思是  你喝醉了
No, I'm just saying, you're wasted.
-你不能开车  -一堆废话
- You can't just drive-- - Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
我听到了
I heard ya.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
什么  特雷弗  我们坐下来吧
What? No. Trevor, let's just sit down, okay?
我们...
We'll--
你  你没听见那声音吗
You-- you don't hear that?
特雷弗  什么也没有
Trevor, there's nothing there.
好吗  我们坐下来吧  然后
All right? Let's just sit down, and we'll all just--
搞什么...
What the...?
快跑  快跑
You got to run. You got to run!
特雷弗
Trevor!
抱歉  不过你弟弟在嗑什么药啊
I'm sorry, but what is your brother on?
特雷弗
Trevor!
特雷  别闹了  别那么讨厌
Trev, come on. Stop being a tool.
走吧  特雷  我们回去吧
Come on, Trev. Let's head back.
兄弟
Dude.
[邪恶力量 第7季第18集]
女士们
Ladies.
你想怎么样  飞行员
What do you want, top gun?
首先  希望你们放尊重点
For starters, i'd like a little respect.
抱歉  警官  我们没想到
Sorry, officer. We didn't realize.
我原谅你们  坐吧
All's forgiven. Take a seat.
告诉我那晚在寡妇岭特雷弗·麦凯的事
Tell me about Trevor McAnn. Other night up at Widow's Peak.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - All right.
-当时很怪  -一开始他好像
- It was weird...  - Well, at first it was just like
-他喝得烂醉  -他喝得烂醉
- cause he was super-drunk. - he was super-drunk.
你先说
You. Go.
是詹妮·格林奇
It was Jenny Greentree.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好吧  那不过是个愚蠢的传说
Okay? She's just a dumb legend.
-等等  谁  -詹妮·格林奇
- Hold up. Who? - Jenny Greentree.
我爸说她真的在森林里丧命了
My dad says she really died in the woods.
被安葬在镇上的墓园里
And she's buried in the town cemetery.
好吧  詹妮·格
All right, Jenny G.
你休想再害人了
Your ganking days are over.
你被盖思秒杀了
You've been Garthed.
雷  你在哪
Ray, where are you?
你现在该和家人在一起
You should be with your family right now.
拜托  别做傻事
Don't do anything stupid. Please.
搞定了  怨鬼安息了
Yeah, I clocked out. Put it to bed.
问题解决
Problem solved.
我要上你那去  所以
And I'm headed your way, so, uh...
浴缸里放好热水
fire up that hot tub.
不对  我更爱你
No, I heart you more.
在寡妇岭发现被弃车辆
Abandoned vehicle out by Widow's Peak.
又发现一具尸体
Uh, we got another body up here.
这人被撕成碎片
Guy's torn to shreds.
什么
What?!
不会吧  怎么可能  我秒杀她了
No way. How is that possible? I garthed her!
好吧  如果他醒了或是别的情况
All right, well, call us if he wakes up
麻烦打给我们
or, you know, anything.
好
Yeah, fine.
谢谢你帮忙  梅格
Thanks for your help, Meg.
贱人
What a bitch.
小卡没有好转了
So, Cass is the same, then?
是啊  糟透了
Yeah, down to the drool.
对了  你的脑袋怎么样了
By the way, how is your custard?
挺好  越来越好了
It's all right. It's getting better.
希望别像《午夜凶铃》那盘录像带似的
Just wish it wasn't like the damn tape from "The ring."
我没事是因为把疯狂传给别人了
I mean, I feel like I'm okay 'cause I passed on the crazy.
不是这样的  你听到小卡怎么说了
No, you didn't. You heard what Cass said.
我们就别说了  好吗
Let's -- let's not. You know what?
你好
Hello.
你好  迪恩  我是盖思
Hey, Dean. It's Garth.
-等下  你是谁  -盖思
- Wait. W-who is this? - Garth.
盖思·菲茨杰拉德四世
Garth Fitzgerald iv.
之前合作杀恶魔
We worked together on that demon thing?
我救你一命
You owe me one?
对
Oh, yeah.
对  你怎么样  盖思
Yeah, how you doing, Garth?
兄弟  我需要你来帮我
I'm ready to cash in that chip, bro.
堪萨斯章克申城出事了
There's something brewing in Junction city, Kansas.
就在这儿
Well, this is it.
先生们  这就是布朗下士
Gentlemen... this is Corporal Brown.
詹姆斯·布朗下士
Corporal James Brown.
我正要去玛亚纳空军报道
I'm shipping off to the A.F. Mayana.
我是来悼念我的堂弟
I'm here to pay respects to my cousin
因为我没法出席他的葬礼
as I will not be able to attend the funeral.
对你家人来说打击一定很大
That must be terrible for your family.
接连失去两兄弟
Losing two brothers so fast.
是的  是的  我姑姑  她
Yeah. Yeah. My aunt -- she's, uh...
她为此心都碎了
She's real broken up about it.
医生  我们能看看两人案卷吗
Hey, doc, can we see both files, please?
我太太  我就在办公室
This is my wife. I'll, uh, be in my office.
好
Great.
你没说他们是兄弟
You didn't say they were brothers.
伙计  我才知道又死人的事
Dude, I just found out about the other corpse,
想快点行动
and...started moving quick.
我在四处打探呢
I'm sucking up info as I go.
干嘛  你对西装过敏吗
What, are you allergic to a suit?
不是  我只是穿军装更好看
No. I just... look good in a uniform.
没错  死因相同
Yep. Same cause of death.
对  夜里在森林里被人剖腹
Right, uh, gutted at night in the woods,
传说詹妮·格林奇的鬼魂在那里游荡
where legend says that the ghost of Jenny Greentree roams.
我检测过电磁波了
Oh, uh, I already scanned for EM...F.
我想我的可能又坏了
I guess mine must be broken again.
好吧  我信你了
All right. I'm reading your mail.
-詹妮什么的鬼魂  -格林奇
- Uh, ghost of Jenny...whatever? - Greentree.
问题就在这儿  我烧了她的尸骨
That's just it. I torched her bones.
也许她还有什么东西留存下来了
Yeah, well, maybe she's got something still laying around.
深表怀疑  她当时无家可归
Highly doubtful. Chick was homeless.
再说难道只有我觉得这不像恶灵
Plus, is it me, or is this less evil spirit,
更像是怪物咬死的
more monster chow?
狼人
A werewolf?
不过目击者称
Except the witness said
追杀第一个死者的东西是隐形的
that whatever was chasing victim numero uno was invisible.
隐形鬼魂狼人
Uh so, invisible ghost werewolf?
不然我为什么要叫你们来支援
Why'd you think I called for backup?
你们听说过高乐麦芽酒吗
Either of you ever heard of Thighslapper Ale?
是脱衣女郎还是什么饮料
Is that a stripper or a beverage?
二逼货喝的饮料
Beverage for douchebags.
太平洋西北部销量第一的微酿啤酒
Uh, number one microbrew in the Pacific Northwest.
但我们在堪萨斯
But we're in Kansas.
我不说了  你什么意思
Yeah, I rest my case. What's your point?
这老板是死去两兄弟的爸爸
The owner is the Dad to the dead brothers.
好吧
Right.
我换下军装  扮上联调局探员
I'll can the uniform, go Fed.
四十分钟后啤酒厂见
See you at the brewery in 40.
对他的好感是慢热型的
He grows on you.
探员们  我叫玛丽  是这里的经理
Agents. I'm Marie. I'm a manager.
感谢你能在周日赶过来
Thanks for coming in on a Sunday.
我们愿意帮忙  什么事都行
We want to help. Anything we can do.
这都是你爸的产业吗
Oh. So all this is your dad's, huh?
还有他朋友  兰迪·巴克斯特
And his friend-- Randy Baxter.
他们现在共有这里
they own the place together now.
现在
Uh..."now"?
就是戴尔死后
Well, since Dale died.
等下  等下  等下
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
你们以为我想多晚来就多晚来吗
You think I just come in late whenever I want?
对不起  先生  不会再发生了
I'm sorry, sir. It won't happen again.
他是"魅力十足"的兰迪·巴克斯特
The, uh, "Charming" Randy Baxter.
我告诉你
I'll tell you what
恭喜  你现在得值夜班了
Congratulations. You're headed for the graveyard shift.
迟到一秒钟  你就可以滚了
Be one second late, and you're fired.
好吧  先生
Yes, sir.
他其实是很不错的人
He's actually a really nice guy.
只是管事的都不容易啊
It's just not easy being the axman.
没错
So true.
我同事会跟你谈  我就失陪了
My comrades got you covered, so if you'll excuse me.
我和你一起去
Uh, yeah, I'll go with you.
麦凯先生吗
Mr. McAnn?
我们不会占用你很久  我保证
Uh, we'll be brief. I promise.
麦凯先生  你两个儿子会不会
Mr. McAnn, is there any reason to believe
有什么敌人
your sons may have had enemies?
他们不是被动物袭击了吗
We were told they were animal attacks.
我们只是需要调查所有的可能性
We just need to explore every possibility.
他们有很多朋友
They got lots of friends.
没敌人
No.
他们和你一起在这里工作吗  像玛丽一样
Well, do they work here with you? Like Marie does.
会不会有人嫉妒了
Could someone have been jealous?
没有  只有玛丽在这里
N-no. Marie's the only one.
那个  没有  没有
Okay -- no. Th-- there's no...uh...
吉姆  没事的  没事的
Jim. It's okay. It's okay.
让他休息一下  我来回答你们的问题
Let him get some rest. I'll answer your questions.
好的
Of course.
戴尔死时他就很自责  现在又出了这事
He blamed himself when Dale died, and now this.
他为什么自责
Why did he blame himself?
戴尔比较敏感
Well, Dale was sensitive.
但你也不能时时刻刻盯着他啊
But what do you do -- watch them 24/7?
这不能怪戴尔的朋友
You can't blame Dale's friends.
但你爸爸还是自责
But your dad still feels bad.
戴尔妻子起诉我们使得情况更糟
And it doesn't help Dale's wife is suing us.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why?
她很生气很悲伤  这又是在美国
She's angry and grieving, and this is America?
我很了解雷和特雷弗
I knew Ray and Trevor.
我是吉姆四个孩子的教父
Hell, I'm godfather to all four of Jim's kids.
雷和特雷弗很喜欢寻乐子
Ray and Trevor loved their fun,
但他们从不做什么疯狂的事
but they'd never do anything crazy.
你自己没儿子吗
No regrets of your own?
吉姆的孩子就像我的
Just jim's.
他们会借我的车  扫荡我的冰箱
They'd borrow my car, raid my fridge.
你们俩和第三个合伙人合办这家公司
Now, the two of you started this company with a third partner.
对吗
Right?
对的  戴尔
Yeah. Dale.
他几个月前去世了
He passed away a few months ago.
在森林里去世还是...
Passed away in the woods or...?
自杀
He took his own life.
很遗憾
Sorry.
他有问题不是一天两天了
Well, he had problems for a long time.
这简直是噩梦
Look, this is just a nightmare.
开始是戴尔  现在又是这事
First Dale, now this.
这本该是我们最重要的一年
This was gonna be our big year.
我们要出售高乐
We're selling Thighslapper
卖给美国最大的分销商之一
to one of the largest distributors in the U.S.
已经谈了几个月了
It's been in the works for months.
新闻很快就要公布于众
News is gonna hit public pretty soon.
这是人生的终极目标了
Well, that's the brass ring, huh?
是的  要不是现在这个情况
Given other circumstances, yeah,
我们一定会庆祝的
we'd be celebrating right about now.
看起来很棒  亲爱的
That looks great, sweetie.
-在家吗  -外公来了
- Hello? - There's grandpa. Hi.
我去拿些点心  你应该吃点东西
I'll get some snacks. You should eat.
好
Yeah.
坐吧  爸爸
Sit, dad.
你在画什么呢
Hey, what you drawing?
我的世界
My world.
亲爱的  怎么了
What is it, sweetie?
怎么了
What is it?
莉莉安
Lillian!
晚上出来活动的有爪怪物数都数不清
There's a million things with claws go bump in the night.
一旦加上"隐形"二字  数字就变少了
Once you throw in "Invisible," the number goes down.
"午后偷欢"
"Afternoon delights"?
不是吧  盖思
Really, Garth?
你不觉得这地方有点
Don't you think this place is a little, uh...
办工一天后  谁不想泡个热水澡啊
Uh, you want a nice hot tub after a day at the office.
小事罢了
It's the little things.
真为这酒厂的兄弟感到难过
I feel sad for those brewery dudes.
花费一生利用啤酒来美化世界
Spend your life beautifying the world through beer.
先是合伙人自杀
First a partner offs himself.
然后是两个孩子被不知名怪物抓死
Now two kids get ganked by unknown freakadeek.
这上面说  戴尔不仅仅是合伙人
According to this, Dale wasn't just a partner.
他还是个酿酒专家
He was also the brewmaster.
酿酒专家
"Brewmaster"?
他是公认的天才
He was widely considered a genius.
好吧  够了
All right, that's it.
什么微酿啤酒也配不上
No microbrew is worth...
什么来着  八本美食杂志大奖
...what was it -- eight food magazine awards?
啤酒不是食品  它是  水
Beer's not food. It's...whatever water is.
高乐
Thighslapper.
这酒真不错
Wow, that's actually awesome.
该死  我都不生气了
Damn it, I'm not even mad anymore.
开怀畅饮啊  盖思
Party on, Garth.
我通常不喝啤酒
I don't even usually drink beer.
它会影响我的深度知觉
It messes with my depth perception.
特别是我裸泳的时候
Especially when I skinny-dip.
你们想听笑话吗
Hey, you guys want to hear a joke?
听着  有件事很有意思
Listen to this. This is something interesting.
盖思  你醉了吗
Garth, are you drunk?
伙计  我刚刚喝完了一整瓶啤酒
Dude, I just... drank a whole beer.
我当然醉了
Of course I'm drunk.
什么有意思的事情
"Something interesting."
对
Right. Uh...
我能再来点高乐吗
Hey, can I have some more Thighslapper?
-不行  -不行  你只能喝咖啡美女
- No. - No. Coffee for you, Tara Reid.
爱尔兰咖啡行吗
Coffee with ---- in it?
这上面说实际上戴尔在死前
So, it says that Dale actually left the company
两周就离开了公司
two weeks before he died.
或许  因为不想出售而被赶走了
Or...maybe he got pushed out 'cause he didn't want to sell.
巴克斯特说交易已经谈了数月了
I mean, Baxter said the deal's been in the works for months.
这就说明了那个遗孀为何要起诉
That would explain the widow. She's suing.
也许戴尔对此不满  而且怨气依旧
Maybe Dale had a bone to pick, and he's still picking it.
没错  也许他阴魂不散
Right. So, maybe he's a spirito Malo.
各警队速到麦凯宅邸  沃什伯恩698号
Unit to McAnn residence. 698 Washburn.
"麦凯的宅邸"  是吉姆·麦凯吗
"McAnn residence," as in Jim McAnn?
看在他们的份上
As in, let's hope for their sake
希望我们的幽灵没离开森林
our spirito ain't made it out of the woods.
好吧
All right.
我们去看看吧
Let's go check it.
你们俩去吧  我去拜访下那个遗孀
Uh, you two go. I'm gonna visit the widow.
-怎么样  -这地方没问题
- So? - Place is clean.
我的电磁感应器什么都没有  这个也是
My EMF is a nada. So is this one.
-那是我的吗  -是的
- Is that mine? - Yeah.
我借来一用  以防我的坏了
I borrowed it in case mine's broke.
那么
So, uh...
我们要找的还是隐形狼人吗
We still on invisible werewolf?
也许是  也许不是  我没法让苔丝开口
Maybe, maybe not. I can't get Tess to talk.
但我感觉她看到了什么
But I get the feeling she saw something.
我去和她谈一轮
I'm gonna take a run at her.
-一轮  -相信我
- A what? - Trust me.
我的特别女士有个双胞胎
My special lady has twins.
麦凯先生
Mr. McAnn?
"特别女士"
"Special lady."
能让我们单独和苔丝谈一会吗
Do you mind if we speak to Tess alone for just a sec?
会很有帮助的
It would really help.
宝贝  我们
Honey, we'll...
我们就在那边  好吗
We'll be right out there, okay?
谢谢
Thanks.
你好  苔丝
Hi, Tess.
你想告诉我今晚看见什么了吗
You want to tell me what you saw tonight?
或许你想和
Or maybe you'll talk to...
费佐先生谈谈
...Mr. Fizzles!
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend!
盖思  把袜子放一边去吧
Garth. Why don't we put the sock away?
费佐先生想要帮助苔丝
Mr. Fizzles wants to help Tess.
他想要倾听
He wants to listen.
费佐要去不见天日的地方
Mr. Fizzles is gonna go where the sun don't shine.
是个怪物
It was a monster.
苔丝  我相信你
I believe you, Tess.
它有爪子吗
Did it have claws?
苔丝  为什么你是唯一能看见的人呢
How come you were the only one that could see it, Tess?
还有什么呢  苔丝
What else, Tess?
你确定吗
You sure?
因为费佐先生能看出来你在
'Cause Mr. Fizzles can sense when you're being a...
说谎
...liar.
行了  够了
All right. That's -- that's enough...
费佐先生
Mr. Fizzles.
我喝了大人的饮料
I drank a grown-up drink.
大人的  咖啡吗
Uh, grown-up like, uh, coffee?
你是说酒吗
Well, you mean alcohol?
我不是有意的
It was an accident.
别让他们逮捕我  费佐先生
Don't let them arrest me, Mr. Fizzles.
你丈夫去过很多地方吗
Your husband did a lot of traveling, huh?
为找最好的配料他去了国外许多地方
He went to all kinds of exotic places for the best ingredients.
我喝过他酿的酒  非常棒
Right. I've tried his work. It's -- it's great.
我听说你跟戴尔以前的合伙人
Um, I hear you're not exactly on the best of terms
有些不愉快
with Dale's old partners.
他们背着他出售了他的公司
Well, they sold his company right out from under him.
不是为了钱  是为了
It's not about money. It's about...
酒厂就像他的孩子
It was his baby, you know?
你好像对此挺生气的
You sound pretty upset about it.
我气死了  恨死他们了
I'm furious. I hate them.
然而我又想到了戴尔是个怎样的人
But then I think how Dale was.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他的朋友们抛弃了他  你知道他怎么说
His friends left him behind, but you know what he said?
"我要送他们一件礼物以示我对他们的宽恕"
"I'm gonna send them a gift that shows I forgive them".
你知道他送了他们什么吗
Do you have any idea what he sent them?
一瓶日本米酒  他旅游时带回来的
Bottle of saki. From one of his trips.
装在一个上面有手写字的华丽盒子里
In a...gorgeous box with writing.
他对这东西可小心了  连我都不让碰
He was so careful with it. Wouldn't let me touch it.
树林里那个孩子看到了别人看不到的东西
So, kid in the woods sees something that nobody else does.
然后苔丝看到了一个怪物  而吉姆没看到
Then Tess sees a monster, and Jim doesn't.
这是怎么回事呢
What's the thread?
有些变种人能看到红外线
Well, certain mutants see infrared.
"大人的饮料"
"Grown-up drinks".
苔丝喝了妈妈的酒  而第一个死者也喝得烂醉
Tess chugged her mom's, and vic number one was plastered.
没错  也就是说
Right. So...
得喝醉才能看到怪物  好酷
Whoa. Monster you got to be drunk to see. Cool!
不过  也很难消灭
Also... hard to fight.
就是热热身
Just getting in the zone.
你只能喝果酒
You are strictly on wine coolers.
我喜欢果酒  我就喜欢甜的东西
Hey, I love those. Anything sweet.
这个难看的酒瓶是怎么回事  幸运符吗
So, uh, what's with the grody flask anyway? Lucky charm?
这是鲍比的
It's Bobby's.
什么微酿啤酒也配不上  什么来着  八本...
No microbrew is worth-- what was it-- eight...
是吗
Really?
是这样的
'cause, um...
你觉得有没有可能
You think there's a possibility
是鲍比在扰乱你的电磁场信号
that Bobby's riding your wave?
不可能  我们把他火化了
No, we gave him a hunter's wake.
我烧了我表弟布兰登的尸骨
Yeah, I-I burned my cousin Brandon,
而他还是在人世游荡
and he stayed stuck.
还有还有  印度也有鬼
And-- and-- and they got ghosts in India,
而且他们所有人都是火葬的
and they cremate everybody over there.
只是直觉  不过也许这里的确有电磁场
It's just instinct, but maybe there is EMF around here.
但与这案子无关
It just ain't the job.
好了  别谈论这个了  行吗
All right, we're not gonna talk about this, okay?
别在工作时说
Not in the middle of work.
抱歉
Sorry.
只是希望火化烧到位了
Just hope that fire did the trick.
萨姆
Hey, Sam.
好的  知道了  我们就来
Yeah. Got it. We're on our way.
在这儿呢
Here it is.
等一下
Oh. Wait a second.
有人一直在偷酒喝
Someone's been sampling the goods.
可不是
Oh, you don't say?
快看
Hey, check it out.
天呐  我爱死偏执狂了
God, I love paranoid people.
看你能不能登上电脑
See if you can get on.
好吧
Okay. Uh...
好了  第一起死亡是什么时候
All right, so, first death was, what,
四个月前  是吗
four months ago? Yeah?
没错  特雷弗·麦凯  第一个死者
Mm-hmm, and, uh, Trevor Mcann. Patient zero.
他到底从那瓶子里放出什么来了
So, what did he let out of that bottle?
什么都没有
Nothing there.
是我们看不到
That we can see.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
喝吧
Tick-tock.
你还能喝醉吗
I mean, can you even get drunk anymore?
对你来说喝酒就和喝维生素一样吧
It's kind of like drinking a vitamin for you, right?
闭嘴
Shut up.
-好了  开始吧  -好吧
- All right. Party time. - Okay.
倒带再放
Rewind and go.
他把这东西放出了盒子
So, he-- he let that thing out of the box,
它肯定是跟着他
and it must have just followed him
去那个闹鬼的地方了
to the place with all the thingies.
没错  就是这样
Yes. Yes.
真是高招
That's smart.
我还真有点醉了
I'm actually kind of drunk.
这是什么酒
What is this?
我喜欢
Me likey.
真怀念这么说话
I miss these talks.
搞什么
What the hell?!
糟糕  关掉它  快关了
Oh, man. Turn it off. Turn it off.
还联邦探员呢
FBI, huh? You know what?
你们跟警察扯淡吧
You can save it for the cops.
巴克斯特先生  听我说  请你听我们解释
Mr. Baxter, listen. If you just let us explain, you might...
911  有什么紧急情况吗
911. What's your emergency?
你好  需要帮忙吗
Hello? Do you need assistance?
[日语]
"Anata ga marou mono...
wa anata ka ra mo morau".
上面说"我将夺走你们从我这儿夺走的东西"
It says, "What you took will be taken from you".
差不多就是以牙还牙
Like, eye for an eye.
听得懂吗
You with me?
[日语]
"Kono bin niwa
syoujou zuke no sake ga hu-in sarete iru".
这东西你们到底是哪里弄来的
Where'd you guys get this anyway?
怎么了  有关系吗
Why? Is there, uh, something the matter?
你们不迷信吧
Well, you're not superstitious, are you?
-完全不  -不迷信
- Not at all. - No, no.
这上面说里面的瓶子里有个酒仙
Because... this says the bottle inside contains a Shojo.
酒仙是什么
What's a... Shojo?
酒幽灵
An alcohol spirit.
就是个古老的神话  换了我不会担心的
Look, it's just an old myth. I wouldn't worry about it.
只是这东西可不太友好
But they are not known for being friendly.
我得走了
I got to go.
给你钱
Oh. Uh, hey... there you go.
-谢谢  -谢谢  保重
- Thank you. Yeah. - Thank you. Take care.
盖思
Garth.
巴克斯特呢
Where's Baxter?
对了  这家伙可比看上去要重得多
Dude's a lot heavier than he looks, F.Y.I.
给你
But here.
我猜你会想要回这个的
Thought you might want this back.
你塞住全美最二逼的微酿啤酒执行总裁的嘴
You have the C.E.O. of the douchiest microbrew in the U.S.
把他放在你的浴缸里
gagged in your hot tub?
你觉得这会有好下场吗
You really think that's gonna end well?
你们太不有爱了吧
I'm not feeling the love.
好了  酒仙
All right. Shojo.
看看能查到什么
Uh, let's see what we can see.
酒仙是什么
What's Shojo?
日本酒怪
Japanese booze monster.
大概这就是喝醉才能看到它的原因
I guess that would explain why you got to be drunk to see it.
真有诗意
Very poetic.
好怕怕哦
Ooh. Creepy.
好了  上面说酒仙在有很多酒的地方游荡
Okay. So, a Shojo is said to roam where there's lots of alcohol.
民间传说  在过去的日本
There's lore saying that, back in the old day,
如果你醉得厉害
if you were plastered enough,
就能看到一个酒仙躲藏在酿酒厂附近
you could see one skulking around the breweries in Japan.
那这个为什么要撕了酿酒商的孩子
Yeah, but why is this one shredding brewers' kids?
你可以用正确的咒语盒
Apparently, you can harness the will of a Shojo
来控制酒仙的意志
with the right spell box.
然后你基本上就有了一条攻击犬
Then you basically have an attack dog
可以帮你完成
that you can sic on whatever
你任何的复仇任务
sort of personal revenge mission you want.
所以戴尔弄了一个来惩罚他的朋友们
So Dale nabs one to punish his pals.
送去这个瓶子  早晚都有人要打开喝的
Send the bottle, sooner or later it's popped open.
然后就有了一个酒仙
Then you have a Shojo
它会做任何戴尔写在这个盒子上
that will do whatever Dale compelled it to do
强迫它做的事
right here on the box.
等等
Wait.
但它杀的不是背叛了戴尔的人
Except it's not killing the people that screwed him over.
戴尔的妻子说  公司就是他的孩子
Well, Dale's widow said the company was his baby.
如果他真想让朋友们感受他所感受的痛苦
So, if he really wanted his friends to feel what he felt...
他就会夺走他们的
He would take theirs.
他们的孩子  至少是吉姆的孩子
Well, their kids. Jim's, anyways.
巴克斯特是他们的教父
And Baxter was the godfather.
好了  直接说我们怎么对付它吧
All right, skip to how do we gank it.
-好消息  它是可以消灭的  -但是
- Good news. It is killable. - But...
但只能用受到日本神道教赐福的武士刀杀了它
but only with a samurai sword consecrated with a Shinto blessing.
这可不是什么好消息
Well...that's not a silver lining.
酒仙早就已经把该杀的都杀了  对吧
The Shojo already cleaned house, right?
玛丽是最后一个还活着的目标了
I mean, Marie's the last target standing, so...
我去当铺  找找看那把剑
I'll hit the pawn shops and, uh, look for the sword.
你去盯着玛丽
You babysit Marie.
抱歉
Yikes. Sorry.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
除非我没错
Unless I've got nothing to be sorry for.
盖思
Garth.
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
我担心鲍比也许一直跟着你们
I'm concerned that Bobby might be haunting you.
我和迪恩说过  他不让我再说
I brought it up to Dean, and he shot me down.
盖思  闭嘴
Garth! Leave it alone.
-没事  -不  有事
- It's okay. - No, it's far from okay.
我已试过和鲍比联系
I've already tried contacting Bobby.
我那瓶酒凭空消失了  我就用了碟仙
When that beer disappeared, I pulled out a talking board.
不叫上我
Without me?
我当时想  何必拉你一起
You know, I figured, why drag you in...
反正我自己也能做好这事
when it's something I could just put to bed myself.
然后呢
And?
如果他在的话  我就会告诉你了
And if he was there, I'd have told you.
晚点再说  你跟着玛丽
Talk about this later. You follow Marie.
你的钥匙借我
Let me borrow your keys.
我是想帮你的  巴克斯特先生
I'm trying to help you, Mr. Baxter.
你是谁
And who the hell are you?
好了  我很疑惑
Now, I'm confused.
戴尔戳中了你们的痛处
Dale goes to get you all where it hurts--
你们的孩子
The kids.
只不过  你没有孩子
Only, you don't have any kids.
这还是伤我很深  相信我
It still affects me. Believe me.
你到底在隐瞒什么
You want to tell me what you're hiding?
隐瞒
Hiding?
告诉我
Tell me this.
你上次给员工三次机会是什么时候
When was the last time you gave an employee three chances?
-可能从未有过  -正确
- Probably never. - Exactly.
你是管事的  对吧
You're the axman, right?
这活儿不好干  但是总得有人做啊
Tough job, but, hey, somebody's gotta.
那你为什么给那个懒鬼清洁工多次机会
So, how come you cut that slacker janitor so many breaks?
我  我不知道
I--I don't know.
是  我搜索过了
Yeah. Well, I googled.
结果发现了他妈妈
Come to find his mother...
很早之前是你的秘书
was your secretary way back in the day.
当然啦  你当时已婚了  所以...
Of course, you were married to Mrs. B., so, uh...
你肯定没干出格的事  对吧
No way there's anything naughty there, right?
你到底要怎样才肯说出来
What do you need to get?
不管戴尔知不知道
No matter what Dale knows about you,
在外面四处杀孩子的鬼可知道
'cause that thing out there killing the kids -- it knows!
我和他妈妈并不是和平分手的
It didn't end well with his mom.
她要我发誓永远不告诉他真相
She made me swear never to tell him.
这秘密守不住了
So much for that.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
他啊  他在啤酒厂
He's, uh -- he's at the brewery.
上晚班
Working the graveyard shift.
给你
Here.
如果你还有那么一丝关心那孩子
If you care about that kid at all,
先别叫警察来抓我
don't call the cops on me just yet.
上面说  最好在流水下做这事
It says it's best to do this in a running spring.
好好  有水
Uh, yeah. I, uh -- I got it.
好  行了吗
Okay. We good?
我尽力
I'll do my best.
很好
All right.
[日语]
"Shichihukujin..."
放水
Go.
[日语]
"Hito no teni rori korekara
Seitoun yakuwari wo hatasu kono ken wo tataer."
行了
That's it.
好了  谢谢你  给
All right. Uh, thanks. There.
-谢谢你  -好的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
你好  盖思
Hey, Garth.
迪恩  巴克斯特有个私生子
Dean, Baxter's got a secret love child!
这个酒仙可能会先去找他
The shojo might come for him first!
慢点说
Whoa, slow down!
我可是要救人命啊
I'm trying to save lives here!
你喝醉了吗
Are you drunk?
见鬼
Damn it!
Damn it.
盖思
Garth?
你把手机掉了吗
You dropped the phone, didn't you?
喂喂
Hello.
盖思
Garth!
对不起对不起  我在呢
Sorry, sorry, sorry. I'm here.
你在哪
Where the hell are you?
我在啤酒厂呢
I'm in the brewery.
盖思
Garth?
迪恩  它在这儿
Dean. It's here.
喂喂喂  你干什么
Whoa, whoa, hey! What the hell?!
想活命就跟我走
Come with me if you want to live!
说
Yeah.
你能开车吗
Hey, you good to drive?
搭车  那鬼东西在啤酒厂
Well, get a ride. It's at the brewery.
什么
What?
还有个孩子  别想了  赶紧出发
There's another kid. Don't think -- move.
等等  等等
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
出租车  喂喂喂
Taxi! Hey, hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey!
停下  等等我
Stop! Hold on, hold on.
国家安全大事  请让让
National security! Please!
谢谢您  女士  添麻烦了  谢谢
Thank you, ma'am. Sorry. Thanks, guys.
好  去啤酒厂  赶紧出发
Okay. Brewery. Step on it!
什么
What?
啤酒厂  快点
The brewery! Hurry!
你快点行吗
Hurry. Hurry, hurry. Please?
好  但我喜欢慢慢开
Uh, yeah, but I like to drive safe, you know.
老兄  这是怎么啦  你是谁
Dude, what's going on? Who are you?
我是执法人员  孩子  跟我走
I'm the law, son. Now, follow me.
你是不是醉了  老兄  滚开
Are you drunk, dude?! Get away from me!
好吧  我直说了  巴克斯特是你父亲
All right. I'll just shoot. Baxter is your father.
巴克斯特背叛了戴尔
Baxter screwed Dale.
戴尔套住了一个只有在醉酒后
Dale roped this Japanese monster
才能看得见的日本鬼
you can only see when you're drunk,
现在它来杀你了
And now it's here to kill you.
等等  巴克斯特是我父亲
Whoa, wait a minute. Baxter is my father?
你在看哪啊
What are you looking at?
见鬼  跑
Damn it, run!
老兄  那儿什么都没有啊
Dude, there's nothing there!
咱们得赶紧出去  老兄  有鬼
We got to get out of here, man. It's here!
盖思在哪儿
Where's Garth?
-谁  -盖思
- Who?! - Garth!
有个家伙被砸昏了
There was a guy -- he got knocked out!
天哪天哪
Oh. Oh, god.
-站在我身后  快  -好好好
- Stay behind me. Stay behind me. - Okay, okay, okay.
怎么  你看得见它
What, you can see it?
是  我现在喝醉了  你就...
Yeah. I'm skunked. Just...
-消防出口  数到三  好不  -好
- Fire exit. On three. All right? - Okay.
好吧  换个法子
Okay. So much for that.
退后
Get back!
-它在哪儿  -往右边砍
- Where is it?! - S-swing right!
是我的右边
My right.
三点方向  迪恩
3 o'clock, Dean!
六点方向
6 o'clock!
你还好吧
You okay?
我还活着
I'm alive?
-不是吗  -萨姆
- Yeah? - Sam?
还好
Yeah.
盖思在哪儿
Where's Garth?
他  他在这边
Well, he's -- he's over this way.
-你能去把他弄来吗  -好
- Could you go get him? - All right.
我都错过什么了
What'd I miss?
这玩意儿自己移动了
This moved.
鲍比
Bobby?
你在这儿吗
Are you here?
来啊  现身啊
Come on, do something.
你们真的不想一起去逛逛吗
You sure you guys don't want to hang out?
吃顿早午餐  或许喝点啤酒
Grab some brunch, maybe some brews?
很诱人  但我们得滚了
Tempting but, uh, we better roll.
那么  好吧
All right, well...
好吧
Yeah.
随时联系
Call me anytime.
-好的  -还有你  萨姆
- All right. - And, Sam.
好的
Yeah.
走一个
Aw, come here.
好吧
Uh...yeah.
谢谢你  盖思
Thanks, Garth.
再见了  朋友们
Sayonara, kemo sabes!
好车
Nice ride.
你说得对
You're right.
确实是慢热型的
He has grown on me.
好了  咱们来谈谈
All right. Um... so, let's talk about it.
谈什么
About what?
你是说碟仙的事
Oh. The, uh, talking board?
没关系的  我想我能理解
That's fine. I get it, I guess.
不  不是那个
No. Not that.
我听见你说的话了
Look, I heard you.
我说什么了
Heard me what?
啤酒厂里发生什么了  迪恩
What happened in the brewery, Dean?
没什么  只是我的幻觉
Nothing. It was, uh -- it was just my imagination.
迪恩
Dean...
我知道有事发生
Look, I know something happened.
我希望你能对我坦白
I just want you to be straight with me.
那把剑从屋子另一边飞到我手里
The blade was across the room, and then it was in my hand.
然后我的酒自己没了
And then my beer drank itself.
还有  那页书奇迹般的出现在床上
Oh, and then, that page magically appeared on the bed.
还有  鲍比的书自己掉了下来
And -- and then Bobby's book feel down,
找到小卡那人的号码自动掉了出来
and out popped the number of the guy who found Cass.
-我确定没啥事  -显然的
- Nothing, I'm sure. - Clearly.
那好  你什么意思  萨姆
Well, then, what, Sam?
到底鲍比在不在
Is bobby here or not?!
知道我在想什么吗  迪恩
You know what I think, Dean?
我觉得即使普通人
I think that regular people,
也能到处看到死去的人
they see ones they lost everywhere, too.
没错  那叫鬼
Yeah. Freaking ghosts!
或者只是因为他们太想念那些人了
Or they just miss them a lot.
他们在人群中看到死去之人的脸
I mean, they see a face in the crowd --
而我们则看到书从桌子上掉下来
We see a book falling off the table.
一样的  迪恩  我试过碟仙
Same thing, Dean. I mean, I did the talking board.
我做过多次电磁测试
I ran plenty of EMF.
啤酒消失时  我有点傻了
When that beer went poof, I went a little nuts.
是啊  那你怎么没告诉我
Yeah, and why didn't you tell me?
我说了  那会儿都傻了
Like I said, little nuts at the time.
好吧  如果不是鲍比
All right, well, if it wasn't Bobby,
那是什么玩意儿把剑送到我手里的
then what Jedi'd that sword into my hand?
那个酒仙在屋子对面就能关门
The shojo slammed the door from across the room.
也许它也想去抓那把剑
Maybe it was trying to grab the sword, too.
好吧
Right.
对  如果那是鲍比
Right, I mean, if it was Bobby,
他会让我们知道的
he would let us know.
谁还能比鲍比更懂得做鬼呢
I mean, who knows more about being a ghost than Bobby?
马上会跟我们搞《人鬼情未了》
Instant Swayze, right?
没错
Exactly.
好吧
Okay.
你的意思是  我们好不容易
Okay, so your theory is that -- that we're practically
做了回普通人了
regular people about something for once.
好吧
All right.
想吃顿早午饭  喝点啤酒吗
Well, you want to grab some brunch and some brews?
还是不要了  我还醉着呢
Ugh, no. I'm so hung over.
-还是赶紧上路吧  -好吧
- Let's just hit the road. - All right.
等等
Hang on.
在这儿啊
There you are.
我就在这里呢  你个白痴
I'm right here, you idjit!
该死
Balls!